liberal.org.au 2016-11-07

# Privacy | Liberal Party of Australia

We respect your privacy. 

This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered on the Web sites at liberal.org.au operated by the Liberal Party of Australia (ABN 15 217 882 958). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the Liberal Party Contribute Web site. Usage of the Web site is conditional upon you agreeing to be bound by this Privacy Policy. 

The Liberal Party of Australia recognises the importance of your privacy, and that you have a right to control how your personal information is collected and used. As a registered political party, the Liberal Party of Australia is exempt from the Privacy Act 1988 (Commonwealth of Australia). This Privacy Policy does however seek to comply with the Privacy Act 1988 (Commonwealth of Australia). 

The Liberal Party of Australia will not collect any personal information about you without your consent. We only collect personal information that you tell us about yourself and information about how you use our Web site: eg by registering, when we ask for information such as your email address, name, address and phone number. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that contact. The Liberal Party of Australia also uses cookies to make your use of our Web site and services as convenient as possible. If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. This may mean you will not be able to use the Liberal Party of Australia online services. 

The Liberal Party of Australia will not use or disclose any information unless requested by you, as required by law or if we believe it necessary to provide you with a service you have requested. 

We may contact you at the email or other address which you provide to us in order to provide you with updated information about our Web site, or to contact you in relation to your donation. By supplying your email address to the Party you may from time-to-time receive news and updates via email as well as official correspondence pursuant to the Liberal Party of Australia constitution. 

The Liberal Party of Australia will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. The Liberal Party of Australia will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.
